### **DEDEN KURNIA**

Tangerang, 03 - 05 - 1995
Panunggangan Utara, Tangerang
dedenkurnia001@gmail.com
089663758497

## **Summary**

I am an bachelor information system who has some work experience as an IT support position and programmer. I can operate software, hardware well, developer website, network installation. I have integrity, able to adapt at company, hard worker, and initiative.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Microsoft Office
- PHP Developer
- Wordpress Developer
- Network Installation
- Software & Hardware Installation
- Flutter UI
- SQL
- db2
- SQL server
- MySQL

- HTML
- CSS
- CI

## **Experience**

**IT Staff** - 07/2019 to 01/2021

#### PT. Putra Mustika Prima (MPM Parts)

- Maintenance hardware.
- Troubleshoot hardware software user.
- Monitoring network.
- Asset management IT.
- Inventory management (Microsoft Dynamic AX)

#### **IT Support** - 01/2021 to 02/2021

#### Pasifik group internasional

- Web developer (company profile).
- Graphic design.

#### **IT Admin** - 03/2021 to 12/2022

#### PT. Karya citra cemerlang (KCC)

- Entry data.
- Monitoring stock.
- Troubleshoot hardware software user.

#### IT Support - 01/2023 to 05/2024

#### PT INDO TAICHEN TEXTILE INDUSTRY

- Monitoring stock.
- Troubleshoot hardware & software user.
- Instalasi jaringan LAN
- Instalasi haringan CCTV

# Programmer- 05/2024 to Now PT INDO TAICHEN TEXTILE INDUSTRY

- Menangani debugging dan troubleshooting untuk memastikan program berfungsi dengan baik.
- Mengembangkan sebuah aplikasi atau sistem pada komputer untuk membuat suatu perangkat lunak (software) sesuai permintaan user
- Pengembangan Perangkat Lunak
- Membuat UI Flutter

## **Education**

Bachelor of Computer: Sistem Informasi (2013 – 2018)

Universitas Raharja

Vocational High School: **Software Engineering (2010 – 2013)** 

**SMKN 5 Tangerang**